Gavrie Thompson

Brampton, ON gavrie.thompson@hotmail.co.uk - 647-769-7899

A self-starter with over 6 years' experience working in customer service with ability to build good rapport with others at all levels of management. Able to work independently or as a member of a team with an aptitude for problem solving and multi-tasking and organisational skills. Aiming to secure a challenging position that offers professional growth to gain further knowledge and experience in customer care, product development and marketing.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Brand Ambassador

Mosaic centric field marketing - Toronto, ON -

January 2017 to Present

- Educate consumers on brand while creating a memorable brand experience for our guests, which in turn generates heightened interest about our client's product
- Assist with planning all corporate marketing functions
- Responsible for end of the day reporting (metrics, comments, photos)
- Work with local sales team to coordinate on premise activations
- Attend weekly regional sales meetings
- Leverage social media for networking & promoting activations

Assitant marketing manager

Suave Dance Acedemy - Brampton, ON -

January 2016 to Present

- Promote and driving sales meeting monthly quota
- Creation and implementation of marketing plans, social media strategies, website development, Facebook,
- · Establishing company ad and promotions
- Create online and offline IMC
- Posting Twitter, Instagram and YouTube content
- Branding the business and public image
- Maintain communication via social and all outgoing/incoming platforms
- Develop new revenue streams

Present result using presentation software

Customer Service Agent

Teleperformance - Toronto, ON -

2016 to 2017

- Troubleshooting for cable, internet and phone services
- Identified needs and resolved customer inquiries/requests via telephone and by electronic means within the department standards and guidelines
- Established and maintained effective relationships with both internal and external customers
- Managed all contacts in terms of time spent on resolution, customer expectations and satisfaction, according to specified departmental service level targets
- Responded to complex customer inquiries and complaints in a highly informed, accurate and responsible manner
- Documented all required information in the customer database system

Customer Service Support

IKEA - Vaughan, ON -

2015 to 2017

- Build sustainable relationships of trust through open and interactive communication
- Attracts potential customers by answering product and service questions; suggesting information about other products and promotions
- Retrieving customer accounts by recording account information.
- Resolves product or service problems by clarifying the customer's complaint; determining the cause of the problem; selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem; expediting correction or adjustment; following up to ensure resolution.
- Handling all transaction using POS and computerized cash registers
- Follow communication procedures, guidelines and policies
- Meet personal/team sales targets and call handling quotas

Customer Service Representative

LCBO - Brampton, ON -

2015 to 2015

Responsibilities

- Serve customers promptly, courteously and responsibly
- Operating computerized cash registers
- Follow all LCBO's policies, practices and procedures relating to the customer service standard
- Set and achieved all sales goals
- Unloading delivery trucks
- Handling stocks and floor merchandise
- Operate computerized cash registers
- Lift cases weighing up to 60 lbs/28 kg

Customer service

Gore meadows Community - Brampton, ON -

2013 to 2014

- North of Castlemore Road on The Gore Road
- Worked on concessions cooking and preparing food at a professional level
- Ensure customer accuracy when placing orders

- Experienced in handling cash and credit card transactions while interacting with customers
- Greeting and providing customers with excellent service
- Maintaining detailed, accurate and up-to-date sale reports for daily transactions
- Cleaning using the appropriate tools and equipment
- Supervise and teach ballet, Hip-Hop, Jazz, and contemporary to children ages 4-6
- Coordinate with customers to provide appropriate and meaningful service

EDUCATION

Business Marketing

Humber College - Toronto, ON

September 2016 to June 2018

SKILLS

• Excellent communication skills • Strong customer and public relation skills • Independent worker and co-operative team player • Expert at Twitter, Google+, Facebook marketing and advertising • Mastery of MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook) • Detail oriented • Mobile, content, and email marketing skills • Effective interpersonal skill • Innovative and Analytical Knowledge of CRM • Adobe Creative Suite

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENCES

Smart Serve

First Aid & CPR Level C

ComScore

December 2017 to Present

Google Adwords

April 2018 to Present

Google Analytics

March 2018 to Present